{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418187771","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418187771"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418193789","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418193789"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418210151","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418210150"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418233559","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418233559"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" 41b6aa12-c9ee-42f4-9a7d-91ee6a7509a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_3-4-1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418240069","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418240069"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" 41b6aa12-c9ee-42f4-9a7d-91ee6a7509a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-1-3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418250902","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418250902"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" 41b6aa12-c9ee-42f4-9a7d-91ee6a7509a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_2-4-3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418255530","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418255529"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" 41b6aa12-c9ee-42f4-9a7d-91ee6a7509a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_2-4-3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418261024","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418261024"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" 41b6aa12-c9ee-42f4-9a7d-91ee6a7509a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_3-4-1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418268576","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418268576"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" 41b6aa12-c9ee-42f4-9a7d-91ee6a7509a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_4-3-1"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418269529","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418269529"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" 41b6aa12-c9ee-42f4-9a7d-91ee6a7509a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_1_4-3-1"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418279236","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418279235"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" 11a2e140-9ddf-4b7b-8972-fc32ca5c390e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418279573","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418279573"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" 11a2e140-9ddf-4b7b-8972-fc32ca5c390e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418279651","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418279651"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" 11a2e140-9ddf-4b7b-8972-fc32ca5c390e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418344547","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418344547"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" 0848655b-187b-4b2c-89d9-b00d64cda33c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tena_fisi-za-zake-tena"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" tena"," userResponse":" zake"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418363630","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418363630"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" 0848655b-187b-4b2c-89d9-b00d64cda33c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" tena_fisi-za-zake-tena"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418363700","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418363700"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" 0848655b-187b-4b2c-89d9-b00d64cda33c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418380460","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418380460"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" 0848655b-187b-4b2c-89d9-b00d64cda33c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418380519","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418380519"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" f25f4ccd-7355-4556-892c-53baf63d86e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418446248","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418446248"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" e9635b45-3d87-4a25-a78e-c3d6fd16dfda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tena_za-fisi-zake-tena"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" tena"," userResponse":" zake"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418451538","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418451538"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" e9635b45-3d87-4a25-a78e-c3d6fd16dfda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tena_za-fisi-zake-tena"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" tena"," userResponse":" za"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418455084","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418455084"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" e9635b45-3d87-4a25-a78e-c3d6fd16dfda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tena_za-fisi-zake-tena"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" tena"," userResponse":" tena"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418474359","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418474357"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" e9635b45-3d87-4a25-a78e-c3d6fd16dfda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" tena_za-fisi-zake-tena"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418474446","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418474446"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" e9635b45-3d87-4a25-a78e-c3d6fd16dfda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418486261","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418486261"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" e9635b45-3d87-4a25-a78e-c3d6fd16dfda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418495017","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418495017"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" e9635b45-3d87-4a25-a78e-c3d6fd16dfda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418503004","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418503004"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" e9635b45-3d87-4a25-a78e-c3d6fd16dfda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418512998","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418512997"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418513381","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418513381"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418514036","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418514036"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418514244","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418514244"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418515147","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418515147"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418517477","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418517476"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nichague gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NICHAGUE"," userResponse":" NICHAGUE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418518544","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418518544"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nichague gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418521296","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418521295"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie ndege?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418522379","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418522378"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie ndege?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITUMIE"," userResponse":" NITUMIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418523111","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418523110"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie ndege?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418526006","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418526006"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege inaruka juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418526989","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418526988"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege inaruka juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INARUKA"," userResponse":" INARUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418527688","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418527688"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege inaruka juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418528454","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418528454"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege inaruka juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418530679","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418530679"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami naogopa kuruka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMI"," userResponse":" NAMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418531454","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418531452"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami naogopa kuruka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAOGOPA"," userResponse":" NAOGOPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418531921","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418531920"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami naogopa kuruka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418536721","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418536720"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nitumie helikopta?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AU"," userResponse":" AU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418537504","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418537503"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nitumie helikopta?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITUMIE"," userResponse":" NITUMIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418538633","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418538632"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nitumie helikopta?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" HELIKOPTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418541707","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418541706"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418542561","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418542560"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" HELIKOPTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418542782","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418542781"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418543155","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418543154"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418543301","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418543301"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418543934","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418543933"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWA"," userResponse":" SAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418546880","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418546879"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AU"," userResponse":" AU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418547803","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418547803"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LABDA"," userResponse":" LABDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418548723","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418548722"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITATUMIA"," userResponse":" NITATUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418549366","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418549366"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418549450","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418549450"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418550027","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418550026"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOSHI"," userResponse":" MOSHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418553344","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418553344"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini stesheni iko mbali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418554209","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418554209"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini stesheni iko mbali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" STESHENI"," userResponse":" STESHENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418554654","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418554654"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini stesheni iko mbali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKO"," userResponse":" IKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418555311","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418555310"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini stesheni iko mbali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418555889","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418555888"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini stesheni iko mbali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418558628","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418558628"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitachoka kutembea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITACHOKA"," userResponse":" NITACHOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418559470","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418559470"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitachoka kutembea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418562326","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418562325"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie basi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418563520","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418563519"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie basi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITUMIE"," userResponse":" NITUMIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418564303","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418564302"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie basi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418567531","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418567531"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418567979","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418567978"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" CHETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418568373","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418568372"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINA"," userResponse":" KINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418568818","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418568817"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418569273","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418569272"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418569995","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418569994"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKEE"," userResponse":" PEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418573170","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418573170"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda nitatumia lori kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LABDA"," userResponse":" LABDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418574265","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418574265"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda nitatumia lori kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITATUMIA"," userResponse":" NITATUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418574656","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418574655"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda nitatumia lori kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418575613","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418575612"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda nitatumia lori kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418578869","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418578868"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418579724","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418579724"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418580674","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418580673"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASA"," userResponse":" HASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418581596","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418581596"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418581701","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418581700"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418582425","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418582424"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBEBEA"," userResponse":" KUBEBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418583110","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418583109"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZIGO"," userResponse":" MIZIGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418583836","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418583835"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZITO"," userResponse":" MIZITO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418586636","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418586635"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie baiskeli kusafiri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418587989","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418587988"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie baiskeli kusafiri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITUMIE"," userResponse":" NITUMIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418588803","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418588802"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie baiskeli kusafiri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAISKELI"," userResponse":" BAISKELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418590015","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418590015"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie baiskeli kusafiri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418593190","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418593189"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIJUI"," userResponse":" SIJUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418593743","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418593743"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" IKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418594069","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418594067"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418595039","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418595036"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATANIPATIA"," userResponse":" ATANIPATIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418595811","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418595811"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAISKELI"," userResponse":" BAISKELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418596421","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418596420"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418599257","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418599257"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nijaribu kusafiri kwa mashua?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AU"," userResponse":" AU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418599979","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418599979"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nijaribu kusafiri kwa mashua?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIJARIBU"," userResponse":" NIJARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418600725","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418600725"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nijaribu kusafiri kwa mashua?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418600944","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418600944"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nijaribu kusafiri kwa mashua?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418601687","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418601687"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nijaribu kusafiri kwa mashua?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUA"," userResponse":" MASHUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418604805","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418604805"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi siamini mashua sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418605167","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418605167"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi siamini mashua sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418605888","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418605887"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi siamini mashua sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIAMINI"," userResponse":" SIAMINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418606475","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418606474"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi siamini mashua sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUA"," userResponse":" MASHUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418607062","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418607062"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi siamini mashua sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418609931","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418609930"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua nitakachotumia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AAH"," userResponse":" AAH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418612567","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418612566"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua nitakachotumia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJUA"," userResponse":" NAJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418614045","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418614044"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua nitakachotumia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKACHOTUMIA"," userResponse":" NITAKACHOTUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418617428","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418617428"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITATUMIA"," userResponse":" NITATUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418618113","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418618112"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TREKTA"," userResponse":" TREKTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418619193","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418619193"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418622043","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418622041"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418622161","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418622161"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:D..D.all.10.rand.say.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418637583","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418637583"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418642744","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418642744"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418651132","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418651131"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418659144","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418659143"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418670047","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418670047"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SS_OFF1_INC.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418676512","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418676512"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" c058c402-dc9b-4840-9455-9a0098bfb3e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418687848","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418687848"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" f2ef9491-7161-43ee-989a-19c4cf78b6a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418689855","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418689855"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" f2ef9491-7161-43ee-989a-19c4cf78b6a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418691450","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418691450"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" f2ef9491-7161-43ee-989a-19c4cf78b6a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418693906","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418693905"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" f2ef9491-7161-43ee-989a-19c4cf78b6a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418695473","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418695472"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" f2ef9491-7161-43ee-989a-19c4cf78b6a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418698829","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418698828"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" f2ef9491-7161-43ee-989a-19c4cf78b6a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418698979","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418698979"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" f2ef9491-7161-43ee-989a-19c4cf78b6a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418772436","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418772436"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" f2ef9491-7161-43ee-989a-19c4cf78b6a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418772508","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418772508"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" 36bebdeb-d514-47ad-9adf-b882deefac19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani anageuka mbio na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBIO"," userResponse":" MBIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418778577","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418778577"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" 36bebdeb-d514-47ad-9adf-b882deefac19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Jirani anageuka mbio na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::1..4.SS_OFF1_DES.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418788179","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418788179"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" 36bebdeb-d514-47ad-9adf-b882deefac19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Jirani anageuka mbio na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418802368","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418802367"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" efe637ca-0508-41c9-8160-898082bea069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418803649","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418803649"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" efe637ca-0508-41c9-8160-898082bea069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418803698","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418803698"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" efe637ca-0508-41c9-8160-898082bea069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418911706","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418911706"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" efe637ca-0508-41c9-8160-898082bea069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418911776","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418911776"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" fc730545-c903-4d08-bf2a-4646dc0f5e0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nijaribu kusafiri kwa mashua?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUA"," userResponse":" MASHUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418922739","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418922739"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" 0037cdcb-37d1-4c4a-bd52-2de59c9ea561"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ENDESHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ENDESHA"," userResponse":" ENDESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418927130","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418927130"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" 0037cdcb-37d1-4c4a-bd52-2de59c9ea561"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ENDESHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ENDESHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418928716","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418928716"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" 0037cdcb-37d1-4c4a-bd52-2de59c9ea561"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ELIMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ELIMU"," userResponse":" ELIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418931831","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418931831"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" 0037cdcb-37d1-4c4a-bd52-2de59c9ea561"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ELIMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ELIMU"," userResponse":" START_ELIMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418933844","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418933844"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" 0037cdcb-37d1-4c4a-bd52-2de59c9ea561"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ELIMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ELIMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418935466","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418935465"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" 0037cdcb-37d1-4c4a-bd52-2de59c9ea561"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" EMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418939308","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418939308"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" 0037cdcb-37d1-4c4a-bd52-2de59c9ea561"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" EMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418941323","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418941322"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" 0037cdcb-37d1-4c4a-bd52-2de59c9ea561"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" EMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418941482","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418941482"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" 0037cdcb-37d1-4c4a-bd52-2de59c9ea561"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" EMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SS_OFF1_DES.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418950471","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418950470"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" 0037cdcb-37d1-4c4a-bd52-2de59c9ea561"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" EMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418956467","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418956467"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" 0037cdcb-37d1-4c4a-bd52-2de59c9ea561"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" EMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418976559","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418976559"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" 0037cdcb-37d1-4c4a-bd52-2de59c9ea561"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" EMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418976631","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418976631"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" 11f7c50e-017d-45a3-a854-f80673270149"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548418993782","data":{"timestamp":" 1548418993782"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190125_150934"," gameId":" 029b4c51-d8da-4836-b2a4-9276d64af48c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}